let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "who is the World's Strongest Swordsman?",
    answer: "Dracule Hawk Eyes Mihawk",
    options: [
      "Dracule Hawk Eyes Mihawk",
      "Roronoa Zoro",
      "Ryuma",
      "Kozuki Oden",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Where did Luffy was sent by Kuma?",
    answer: "Amazon Lily",
    options: ["Namakura", "Kamabakka", "Amazon Lily", "Weatheria"],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Who is the leader of Baraku works?",
    answer: "Crocodile",
    options: ["Dragon", "Buggy", "Crocodile", "Kuma"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "In which gear Luffy Defeated Katakuri?",
    answer: "Gear 4 Snakeman",
    options: [
      "Gear 4 Bounceman",
      "Gear 4 Snakeman",
      "Gear 5 Awakening",
      "Gear 4 Tankman",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Name the Devil Fruit which gives Magentic power?",
    answer: "Jiki Jiki no Mi ",
    options: [
      "Mera Mera No mi",
      "Gomu Gomu No mi",
      "Pika Pika No mi",
      "Jiki Jiki no Mi ",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Where did the Tournament held for Mera Mera No Mi?",
    answer: "Dressarosa",
    options: [
      "Dressarosa",
      "Alabasta",
      "Sabody Archipelago",
      "Water Seven",
    ],
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who is the one of the Vice Admiral of Marine",
    answer: "Garp",
    options: ["Sengoku", "Garp", "Kizaru", "Aokiji"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "How many years the strawhats disbanded after Ace's Death?",
    answer: "2",
    options: ["2", "37", "1", "0.5"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Who is the  First Second Division Commander of WhiteBeard Pirates?",
    answer: "Oden",
    options: [
      "Ace",
      "Oden",
      "Marco",
      "Teech",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Who helped Strawhats to invade into the Whole Cake Island?",
    answer: "Pekom",
    options: ["Pedoro", "Pekom", "Pudding ", "Carrot"],
  },
];
 